<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Cosmic Kitty</title>
    <link>/blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Cosmic Kitty</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 10:03:05 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Liberatory Learners</title>
      <link>/blogs/aboutliberatorylearners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 10:03:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/aboutliberatorylearners/</guid>
      <description>What is Liberatory Learners? Liberatory Learners is a space for interdisciplinary play designed to investigate, in a personalized way, each student’s individual curiosities about their world.
Classes incorporate:
 Minecraft Film Vegan Culinary Arts Creative Thinking Literacy Music Movement  Join us Today!    View this post on Instagram         A post shared by Liberatory Learners! (@liberatorylearners)
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instagram</title>
      <link>/blogs/instagramliberatorylearners/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 10:11:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/instagramliberatorylearners/</guid>
      <description>Latest Post: Benjamin Von Wong is an amazing artist who creates masterful works from plastic waste that as he states on his website, &amp;ldquo;make positive impact unforgettable&amp;rdquo;.    View this post on Instagram         A post shared by Liberatory Learners! (@liberatorylearners)
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Youtube</title>
      <link>/blogs/liberatorylearnersyt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 10:07:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/liberatorylearnersyt/</guid>
      <description>Latest Meeting   Podcast Episode with Gary Dušek   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Titties</title>
      <link>/blogs/abouttitties/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 10:01:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/abouttitties/</guid>
      <description>What is Titties?
Titties For Change is a Research Hub Dedicated to Ending Plastic Production Forever Through the Study of Utopian Ideas, Independent Thought, and the Imagination.
We are based in Brooklyn, New York. We host vegan plastic-less pot lucks and open mics.
We sometimes dance on the street together.
We are anti-war, anti-plastic, vegan art collective that creates hybrid spaces to educate, re-create, entertain, heal, and transform to find long term solutions to plastic production, homelessness, poverty, slavery and war by shifting rhetoric from “impossible” to “possible” by changing the world through expression, creative projects, and community outreach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Titties Blueprint</title>
      <link>/blogs/tittiesblueprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 10:00:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/tittiesblueprint/</guid>
      <description>Steps Strategies/steps for eliminating plastic waste     1 Create a network of those committed to eliminating plastic, homelessness, and associated issues   2 Create a pitch for the concept, the resources needed, and the founder   3 Turn empty commercial spaces into hubs for community action   4 Gather important political, business, and non-for-profit figures behind the community space concept   5 Holding Plastic manufacturers accountable via emails   6 Sell donated plastic waste to fund community aid   7 Make a list of alternative products to advertise, distribute, and partner with   8 Create a grant to buy an alternative organic material to replace their plastic inventory (restaurants)   9 Partner with a list of restaurants   10 Create survey for restaurants to determine their single use plastic needs   11 Advocacy for all the different industries that produce plastics   12 Host events to increase awareness on community issues   13 Partner with a list of businesses to supply the community centers   14 Create collaborative private spaces within the community centers for rent   15 Institute mental health care in community centers   16 Create products made from recyclables to sell and raise money for the community centers   17 Endorse and support art and artists that create publicity and advocacy for these social issues   18 Creation of mobile and web apps to facilitate these processes   19 Create platform for coordinating restaurants   20 Create market for all of the various components   21 Create a plan for investors   22 Make a list of supporting non-for-profits that help fulfill the mission of ending plastic production   23 Get people to sign the petition (investors, politicians, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Past Events</title>
      <link>/blogs/pastevents/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 09:56:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/pastevents/</guid>
      <description>video { height: 100vh; width: 100%; object-fit: cover; // use &#34;cover&#34; to avoid distortion position: absolute; }  Nov 2018: Tee2Tote events: making totebags and distributing them at a local Bushwick supermarket.
Dec 2019: C3
Jul 2019: Vegan Potluck
May 2019: Tee2Tote Public Event
Oct 2019: Titties Bag Making Workshop Singapore
Jan 2020: &amp;ldquo;The Struggle and The Promise, a vegan potluck art show.
Feb 2020: Calling the Plastic &amp;amp; Plastic Play Zoom Meetings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Me For Events</title>
      <link>/blogs/bookme/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 09:53:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/bookme/</guid>
      <description>Available for Writing, Music, Modelling, Acting, Workshops, and Speaking Engagements. Link to: Resume
Link to: Resume Page 2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Directing</title>
      <link>/blogs/directing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 09:39:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/directing/</guid>
      <description>Answers and Questions: Singapore      
Other Works:  Like Mold by Shuana Noone - 2012 When the Fire Starts to Burn by Clare Tassinari - 2012 …Like Sisters - 2014 Talk Radio by Eric Bogosian - 2015 From the Hands of Strange Children - 2015 The American of Wisconsin by John Oluwole ADEkoje - 2016 “Principles of Geometry: Filmic Component” Ms Hannah has Shit to Say Ms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Performance</title>
      <link>/blogs/performance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 09:23:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/performance/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Who the Fuck is Cho Chang?&amp;rdquo;    Brooklyn Arts Center - 2018
More Performances:
 Brooklyn Arts Center - 2018 Langston Hughes House - 2019 Frequency Collective - 2019  Brooklyn Bazaar - 2019 Wild Project Theatre - 2019 In Singapore during Quarantine - 2020 In Brooklyn during Quarantine - 2020   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thesis</title>
      <link>/blogs/thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 09:12:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/thesis/</guid>
      <description>“(Between the Streets) In Worcester : Redefining Professional Education in Community Development to Cultivate Empathy through a Community Theatrical Framework” Redefining Professional Education in Community Development to Cultivate Empathy through a Community Theatrical Framework By Chiu Yi Hannah Yukon testing git and all sorts of stuff. This research paper presents an alternative form of conducing Community Development Research. It highlights the gaps that currently exist in professional education with the community development and planning program at Clark University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plays</title>
      <link>/blogs/plays/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 09:11:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/plays/</guid>
      <description>Children&amp;rsquo;s Books and Plays  The Worst Wizard Ever and Other Fairy Tales - Produced at the Worcester Polytechnic Institute in partnership with the Latino Education Institute + students from the Goddard School of Technology - 2015 Peter and the Wolf (An Adaptation) - Produced at the Worcester Polytechnic Institute in partnership with the Latino Education Institute + students from the Goddard School of Technology - 2014 Pillowland WIP  Contact for more information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Series Work</title>
      <link>/blogs/serieswork/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 09:03:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/serieswork/</guid>
      <description>I have written a number of works, with Chapbooks being a focused medium.
 ATOA: A Meditative Poem Through the Alphabet i  Interview   ATOA: A Meditative Poem Through the Alphabet ii Break Up Letters 2018 Break Up Letters 2019 Break Up Letters 2020: Will be out for sale soon.  Find all the work available at Queer-Art.org, Snipfeed.Co, and Square(WIP) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Story Behind Everything is pencil.</title>
      <link>/blogs/mymusicstory/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 08:52:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/mymusicstory/</guid>
      <description>There is still so much I would change on this album. I probably will, sonically at least, some parts stick out in ways that make me cringe, but I said May 6th, which means May 6th. I will need to recover the corrupted files (yes 2 weeks before the completion of this, my laptop &amp;ldquo;couldn&amp;rsquo;t load&amp;rdquo; the original files which made it impossible for Alex to mix and master these tracks the way that a song like BIRDS sounds like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music</title>
      <link>/blogs/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 08:21:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/music/</guid>
      <description>Listen to &amp;ldquo;Everything is Pencil&amp;rdquo; (Youtube)   (Bandcamp) (Spotify) (SoundCloud) (Apple Music) </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
